sixerr.com 2014-12-14

# Privacy Policy - Sixerr: services from $1 to $6

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Thank you for visiting **www.Sixerr.com** (our “Site”). We appreciate the opportunity to interact with you through our website and are committed to both protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you as you visit our Site, as well as how we may use that information and whether we disclose that information to anyone.

**_The Information We Collect and How We Use It_**

Any information we collect on our Site generally falls into the Personally Identifiable Information category.

Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know specifically who you are. In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personally Identifiable Information.

Ordering – When you place an order for products or services, we collect Personally Identifiable Information such as your name, contact details, and other transaction information. We **do not** collect billing information; that is handled via your selected online payment processor, usually Paypal or Payza. We use this information to deliver your order and to communicate with you about the status of your order.

**Sharing Your Information**

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission.

From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Limited Warranty or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.

**Links To Other Web Sites**

Links to third-party Web sites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional information for various other goods and services. If you click on one of those links you will be forwarded away from our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information privacy practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.

**Changes To This Statement**

Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed.

By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use.

Contact Us

If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to privacy@Sixerr.com. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention.

This Privacy Statement was last revised on July 23, 2012.
